Teen Kar Seng

Email: teenkar@gmail.com Based in: Singapore

Phone: (+65) 9722 7928

Professional Summary

I am a recent graduate at Berklee College of Music with a Bachelor of Arts in Songwriting and Producing Music.

I am able to compose, notate, arrange, orchestrate and produce music for a variety of genres and use cases. I am also highly proficient with Pro Tools and experienced in audio editing and mixing. I am also proficient in sound design and have experience working with game audio middleware tools such as Wwise and FMOD Studio.

My other competencies include video editing, graphic design and photography, having graduated with a diploma in Communications & Media Management from Temasek Polytechnic.

Education

Bachelor of Arts, Songwriting and Producing Music, Berklee College of Music, Boston, Massachusetts.

April 2020 - May 2023

• CGPA: 3.99 / 4

Diploma, Communications and Media Management, Temasek Polytechnic, Singapore.

April 2016 - May 2019

• Graduated CGPA: 3.48 / 4

Skills

Avid ProTools
MuseScore
Audiokinetic Wwise
FMOD Studios
Unity Engine (Basic)
Adobe Premiere Pro
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe After Effects

Sound Design
Composition
Orchestration/Arranging
HTML/CSS & JavaScript
Video Production
Photography

Music Production

Microsoft Office

Experience

Freelance Audio Editor

May 2021

• Performed recording, editing and mixing of voice-overs for a college level prototype product design video.

Marketing Intern MediaCorp Pte Ltd, Singapore

April 2018 - September 2018

- Filmed and edited videos for social media marketing.
- Graphic Design to create posters and banners for use on digital website and printed for physical use.
- Collaborated with team members to help expand marketing channels.
- Monitored and analyzed impressions, reach and engagements on social media marketing campaigns.
- Handled social media accounts for company.

Military

National Service, Republic of Singapore Air Force (RSAF)

May 2019 - May 2021

• 2-year mandatory enlistment to the Singapore National Service with the RSAF.

Language

- English (Spoken, Written) First Language
- Mandarin Chinese (Spoken, Written) Proficient

Achievements

- MediaCorp Major Project Prize for Best Major Project Group, 2019
- 3rd Place at POL-ITE Water Polo competition, 2017 & 2018
- The Dream Composition Songwriting Competition Finalist, 2018
- 4th Place at National B Division Floorball competition, 2015
- ABRSM Grade 8 Practical (Piano)
- ABRSM Grade 5 Theory